wegottickets.com 2018-12-30

# WeGotTickets | Simple, honest ticketing | Our privacy policy

This is the privacy policy for WeGotTickets ( **"WGT", "we", "our", "us"** ). This Policy explains how and why we collect and use personal information, and what we do to ensure it is kept private and secure. Please read this policy in conjunction with our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.wegottickets.com/tandc), which sets out the terms on which you may access [www.wegottickets.com](https://www.wegottickets.com/) (our **"Website"** ). 

#### 1\. WHO WE ARE

We are Internet Tickets Limited of 13 Kings Meadow, Ferry Hinksey Road, Oxford, OX2 0DP. You may also know us by our trading name " **WeGotTickets** ". For the purposes of data protection law, we will be a controller of the personal information we hold about you. This means we make decisions about how and why your information is used, and have a legal duty to make sure that your rights are protected when we do so. Other companies in our group are WeGotTickets Limited and SU Tickets Limited. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us by writing to us at our registered address given above, telephoning us on + 44 1865 798792 or contacting us via e-mail at [ info@wegottickets.com](mailto:info@wegottickets.com). 

#### 2\. THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect the following types of personal information: 

**Information you give us**

When you sign up for an account on our Website, we will ask for the following personal information about you: 

  * your name; 
  * your contact details (e-mail address, mobile phone number); and 
  * your billing address; 

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

Details of tickets you have purchased, the fulfilment of your orders, and any communications by telephone, in person or by any other means relating to those transactions will also be stored. We will keep a record of all the tickets you have purchased with us, so you can always look back and see what amazing events you have attended at any time, directly from your WeGotTickets account. 

When you purchase a ticket through our platform, the information you have given to us is passed to our payment processing partner to process according to our instructions. We do keep a copy of this. However, we will never store your card details - these are held by our third-party payment provider. 

When you sell tickets through our platform we securely store the information you have provided to enable us to report on and account for your ticket money. 

Finally, if you have interacted with us via social media e.g. by liking our Facebook page, or connecting with us on Instagram, we may contact you via those platforms. 

**Technical data**

When you visit our Website, we may collect technical data about the device you are using, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type. This is used for system administration and to improve the look and feel of our web presence. 

**Special Category Data (also known as sensitive personal information)**

We do not collect any special categories of personal information about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences. If you have disability requirements we may store the information you provide to us about your disability in order to improve our service to you. 

#### 3\. COOKIES

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or device if you agree. We use the following types of cookies: 

  1. Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our Website or add tickets to your basket. 
  2. Analytical/performance cookies. These cookies allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our Website. This helps us to improve the way both sites work, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. 
  3. Social Media Sharing Buttons. We do use sharing buttons in order to make it easier for you to follow our content via your social media pages. These buttons are third-party cookies which are placed onto your device when you visit our Website. Even without you clicking on the relevant sharing button, these sites are aware that you have visited our Website, and may use this information when building their profile of you, and deciding what advertisements you might like to see. You should check the respective policies of each of these social networks to see how exactly they use your personal information. This process does not involve us collecting or storing any of your personal information ourselves. 

#### 4\. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will only use your personal information when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal information in the following circumstances: 

  1. with your consent; 
  2. where we need to perform a contract with you e.g. when you purchase tickets from us; 
  3. where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party), and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests (see the "Legitimate Interests" section below); or 
  4. where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation. 

If you purchase tickets from us, we will send you periodic e-mails about upcoming shows and other events that we think you might be interested in. You can opt-out of receiving these e-mails at any time by clicking the appropriate link in the e-mail itself, or updating your communication preferences via your WeGotTickets account. 

**We may use personal information held about you in the following ways:**

  * to fulfil ticket orders you place with us; 
  * to advise you of forthcoming shows or other events; 
  * to ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device; 
  * to respond to queries you send us. 

When contacting you for any of the above purposes we may do so by phone or email, unless you tell us otherwise. Your data will be treated in accordance with applicable data protection law. It will not be disclosed to anyone outside of WGT, our group, and any other parties named or described in section 8 below. 

#### 5\. LEGITIMATE INTERESTS

We may rely on legitimate interests to process your personal information, provided that your interests do not override our own. Where we rely on legitimate interests, these interests are: 

  1. to keep our records updated and to study how our Website and other services are used; 
  2. to administer and protect our business and web presence (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting); 
  3. to inform our marketing strategies; and 
  4. to grow our business. 

#### 6\. KEEPING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SAFE

We employ a variety of physical and technical measures to keep your personal information safe and to prevent unauthorised access to, use or disclosure of it. We control who has access to your data (using both physical and electronic means). These means include an electronic firewall and other protection measures that involve virus scanning, installation of security patches, vulnerability testing, backup and recovery planning, security audits and other steps designed to improve data protection. Our staff receive data protection training and we have a set of detailed data protection procedures which they are required to follow when handling personal information. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. We cannot absolutely guarantee the security of the internet, external networks, or your own device, accordingly any online communications (e.g. information provided by email or through our Website) are at your own risk. 

#### 7\. STORAGE AND RETENTION

**Where we store your personal information**

Electronic data and databases are stored on secure servers in the United Kingdom and we do not transfer your personal information outside of the European Economic Area. 

**How long we keep it**

We collect and store personal information for purposes connected with our business. As such, we will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary for those purposes. 

If you buy tickets through our Website, we will keep your account open and retain your personal information for five years from the date of your last log-in. We feel that five years is an acceptable time-period, since some artists may wait years between tours, and many events occur only occasionally. Five years will give you ample time to rebook events you are interested in and keep up with the artists you like over the course of their careers. 

If you are a promoter, venue or another client that sells tickets through our platform, we keep information about our commercial relationship with you for seven years from the date of the last event you sold tickets for through our platform. This is because we may need this data in some way to support a claim or defence in court. That is also the period within which our tax collecting authorities may demand to see and audit our records. 

#### 8\. DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may need to disclose your personal information to third parties. Where we do so, any such disclosure will be on the basis that these third parties are required to keep the data we give them confidential and secure, and will not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for us. 

When you buy a ticket from us, we disclose your name and e-mail address to the venue or promoter who put that ticket up for sale on our Website. We do this for two main reasons: 

  * to allow them to identify you when you arrive at the venue. In the event that another ticketholder has the same name as you, your e-mail address will prove who you are, and that your purchase was legitimate; and 
  * to allow them to send you details of future events, but only if you consent to this. 

You can change your communication preferences at any time via your WeGotTickets account. 

If we choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets, we may disclose your personal information to the new owners of the business. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal information in the same way as set out in this policy. 

#### 9\. DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW

We are subject to the law like everyone else. We may be required to give information to legal authorities if they so request or if they have the proper authorisation such as a search warrant or court order. 

We also may need to retain and disclose certain personal information about you to regulatory authorities and to appropriate agencies to conduct anti-money laundering and trade sanction checks and to assist with fraud prevention. We will disclose this information as is required by law. 

#### 10\. YOUR RIGHTS

We want you to remain in control of your personal information. Part of this is making sure you understand your legal rights, which are as follows: 

  1. where your personal information is processed on the basis of consent, the right to withdraw that consent; 
  2. the right to confirmation as to whether or not we are holding any of your personal information and, if we are, to obtain a copy of it; 
  3. from 25 May 2018, the right to have certain data provided to you in a portable electronic format (where technically feasible); 
  4. the right to have inaccurate personal information rectified; 
  5. the right to object to your personal information being used for marketing or profiling, or on the basis of our or a third party's legitimate interests; 
  6. the right to restrict how your personal information is used; and 
  7. the right to be forgotten, which allows you to have your personal information erased in certain circumstances (though this is not an absolute right and may not apply if we need to continue using it for a lawful reason). 

If you would like further information about any of your rights or wish to exercise them, please contact us using the details given in section 1. 

Please keep in mind that there are exceptions to the rights above and, though we will always try to respond to your satisfaction, there may be situations where we are unable to do so (for example, because the information no longer exists or there is an exception which applies to your request). 

If you are not happy with our response, or you believe that your data protection or privacy rights have been infringed, you should contact the UK Information Commissioner's Office, which oversees data protection compliance in the UK. Details of how to do this can be found at [www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/). 

#### 11\. UPDATING THIS POLICY

We may update this Policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on our Website and we will also revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we hold. 

This policy was last updated on 22nd May 2018
